{
    "subject": "resource/Antz",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Aron_Warner",
    "human_readable": "Antz was produced by Aron Warner.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8625378012657166,
            "question": "Which film was produced by Aron Warner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7001042366027832,
            "question": "Is Aron Warner known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6443657875061035,
            "question": "Who was involved in the production of Antz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5966181755065918,
            "question": "Who produced the movie Antz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49338310956954956,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer who worked on Antz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45981794595718384,
            "question": "What year was Antz released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3965705633163452,
            "question": "What other projects might Aron Warner have worked on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34688615798950195,
            "question": "Was Antz a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17833736538887024,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Antz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.024312889203429222,
            "question": "What are some other notable animated films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Antz was produced by Aron Warner.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7709_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Antz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7709_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Antz a successful film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7709_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other projects might Aron Warner have worked on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7709_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7709_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Aron J. Warner's involvement with the production of various films, including Antz, which is marked as a computer animated hit he worked on at PDI/DreamWorks in 1997. Therefore, the statement that Antz was produced by Aron Warner is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}